at this moment rescue workers are laboring to recover
and identify the remains of Jaja Korda
international businessman
Maverick in the fields of armaments and aviation
among the richest men in Europe
this was Corda's sixth recorded airplane crash
he is survived by 10 children
nine boys one nun
his daughter Liesel
I have appointed you sole heir to my estate
which you may come into sooner rather than later
why it's been six years since our last meeting
I have my reasons which are what
my reasons I'm not saying
I'm saying I'm not saying
quarter land and Sea Phoenician infrastructure scheme
my most important project of my lifetime
our objective disrupting obstructing
impeding crippling Quarter's enterprise in any manner possible
get the hand grenades
today tonight and tomorrow
we're rendezvous with every Titan
and pretend we agree what we already agree
but in fact we don't we can't
call it heads
heads
is this supposed to be here
it was under the lunch trolley
oh dear
who shot you Terry's from out of town
help yourself to a hangover aid
you're very kind
could you imagine falling in love with a man like me
by the way hypothetically
you're drunk on three beers
why are you shooting my ceiling
this is a robbery on behalf
no I understand that
I'm asking about my ceiling
you idiots are destroying a magnificent nightclub
one thing you'll never know because you can't
the truth is it
I recognize this assassin
suicide panel
where's my father take this miserable sinner into the company of god